





Summary

Jump to Section

Aresult-oriented leader with experience in Managing CAM Programming for different verticals like Aerospace, Oil & Gas sector, Automotive, Power sector, Heavy & General Engineering. Over 18 years of global experience inclusive of 7+ years of Pre & Post sale of Mastercam /Vericut / CIMCO/NCsimul software in India & SAARC region and 8+ years of CAM programming experience. Experience in managing diverse range of manufacturing activities such as process and equipment selection, customization of postprocessor & process sheet in Mastercam. Experience in Benchmarking & prove out of components on different types of CNC machines.

Work Experience | Education | IT Skills |

Work Experience

Oceaneering as Sr. Manufacturing Engineer Feb 2020 to Till Date

Responsibilities is to manage the CAM programming dept. Generating NC programs for Oil & Gas Industry components in Mastercam & Edgecam software

Deccan Technologies as Manager CAD/CAM Aug 2019 to Feb 2020

Responsibilities is to manage the CAMprogramming dept. Generating NC programs for General Engineering components.

Expert Global Solutions Pvt Ltd as Manager (Manufacturing Engg.) Apr 2018 to Jul 2019

Responsibilities is to manage the CAMprogramming dept. Generating NC programs for Oil & Gas Industry parts on 3 & 5 axis CNC machine in CAMsoftware and validate it in Simulation & verification software.

^ Back to Top

Education

UG: B.Tech/B.E (Mechanical) from Pune University in 2001 PG: M.Tech (Mechanical) from Pune University in 2006

Important

 Using Free CV Search you have access to featured candidate profiles of Naukri. You can browse through the profiles and email the candidates of your choice directly using the email option provided. To prevent misuse of candidate information, contact details and attached resume of the candidates have been withheld

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version Last Used	Experience
MICROSOFT WINDOWS		
CIMCO		
C AND C++		
Mastercam, Edgecam, Vericut		
NCSIMUL, CIMCO Edit, CNC Calc		
NC Base, Robotmaster		
SOLIDWORKS		

^ Back to Top

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English				
Hindi				
Marathi				
Kannada				

^ Back to Top

Affirmative Action

Work Authorization

Category: General
Physically Challenged: No

Job Type: Permanent Employment Status: Full time

^ Back to Top

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICIClcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQs - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICICIcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.